cwcwebdev.net 2005-05-14

# CWC Web Development Club - Privacy Statement

**

Privacy Statement of CWC Web Development Club 

_Statement No 16797_

**

**

**Information about our Organization and Web site**

**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an organization like CWC Web Development Club . We are based in USA . Our principal activities are: 

  * Club Website 
  * User Group Meetings 

Our privacy policy covers CWC Web Development Club and its Web site: 

** Organization Name:  | CWC Web Development Club   
---|---  
Address:  | CWC Box 137, 2660 Peck Ave.   
City, Zip:  | Riverton , 82501   
State:  | Wy   
Country:  | USA   
Controller:  | Richard Fleetwood   
Web Sites(s):  | http://cwcwebdevclub.survivalring.org   
**

**

**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**

**

You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. 

**

**The services and links of our Web site** ****

**

Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data.

Our Web site does not include links to third party Web service providers. 

**

Automatic Collection of Information 

**

We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. 

We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. 

**

Data Collection and Purpose Specification 

**

We collect the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. 

We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organisations. 

To access the table of personal data collected and purposes for which they are used, please [click here ](file:///C:/Documents%20and%20Settings/raf0112/Local%20Settings/Temporary%20Internet%20Files/Content.IE5/S527STAR/pwstatement\[1\].asp#Table5_2)

We may collect and use personal data for the additional purpose of: We collect volunteered personal data to forge the direction of new website additions and club programs. 

If we wish to use our visitors' personal data for new purposes, we do not give them the opportunity to consent to those new purposes. 

**

Children's Privacy 

**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children. 

We take specific steps to protect the privacy of children by: 

  * making reasonable efforts to ensure that a parent has authorized the collection of the child's personal data 

We do not provide information about our personal data practices in relation to children on our home page, or at those sites on our Web site where we collect personal data. 

**

Disclosure and Visitor Choice 

**

We do not disclose your personal data to our subsidiaries or other organizations. 

**

Confidentiality / Security 

**

We do not give visitors to our Web site the option of using a secure transmission method to send us their personal data. 

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: 

  * unauthorized access 
  * improper use or disclosure 
  * unauthorized modification 
  * unlawful destruction or accidental loss 

All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data. 

We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation. 

**

Access to the personal data we may hold about you 

**

You can ask us, by: 

  * sending an email ( webmaster@survivalring.org ) 

whether we are keeping personal data about you. 

Upon request, which you can indicate by: 

  * sending an email ( webmaster@survivalring.org ) 

We will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, within a month. We will provide the information without any charge. 

We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data: 

  * erased 

We do not reserve the right to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data. 

**

Privacy Compliance 

**

There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. 

There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or organization. 

In order to demonstrate that our privacy policy accords with the above privacy instrument, we are: 

  * voluntarily committed to a Self Assessment procedure 

#### Self Assessment procedure 

Name or designation of the privacy policy person or service  | Federal Trade Commission   
---|---  
URL  | http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/index.html   
Address  | 6th & Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W., Washington, D.C. 20580   
Country  | United States of America   

#### Primary personal data/Business information 

**x** | volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  | collected from public records or bodies   
\-  | collected from private organizations   
  
#### Other personal details and profiling data 

**x** | volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  | collected from public records or bodies   
\-  | collected from private organizations   
  
#### Identifiers 

**x** | volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  | collected from public records or bodies   
\-  | collected from private organizations   
  
#### Specific Data 

\-  | volunteered by each visitor   
---|---  
\-  | collected from public records or bodies   
\-  | collected from private organizations   
  
* * *

* * *
